(忆往昔)
辛格先生
Mr. Singer,
我相信你肯定认识米尔斯警长
I believe you know Sheriff Mills.
是他的灵魂  他的灵魂不见了
It's his soul. It's gone.
萨姆
Sam.
我将给你设一道屏障
I'm gonna put up a barrier.
不要碰这个屏障
Don't scratch the wall.
-你认识我的  -路西法
- You know who I am. - Lucifer.
你好啊  萨姆
Hi, Sam.
我想这是我最好的折磨手段
I think this is my best torture yet.
你从没跑出去过  萨姆
You never left, Sam.
你还在囚笼里
You're still in the cage...
和我一起
with me.
这不可能
This can't be happening.
你的皮囊正在融化  你马上就要爆炸了
Your vessel's melting. You're going to explode.
在炼狱中有着比那些灵魂更加古老的东西
There are things much older than souls in purgatory,
你当时也一并吞下了
and you gulped those in, too.
-更古老的东西是什么  -利维坦
- What older things? - The leviathans.
我  我挡不住他们
I-I can't hold them back!
-挡住谁  -利维坦
- Hold who back? - Leviathan!
小卡
Cass?
小卡  他消失啦
Cass is -- he's gone.
这将会非常非常有趣的啦
Oh, this is going to be so much fun.
(如今)
鲍比
Bobby?
你们有多少人在他体内
How many of you ass-clowns are in there?
一百吗
A hundred?
不止吗
More?
你的皮囊要爆炸了  是吧
Your vessel's gonna explode, ain't it?
还是不要太操劳的好
Wouldn't do anything too strenuous.
换了我  就会收工回家
In fact, I'd call it a day, head on home.
我们会回来找你的
We'll be back for you.
前所未见啊
This is a new one.
你不是真实的
You're not real.
对了
Right.
你还觉得这个梦境是真实的
You think this fruit bat Fever Dream is reality?
你回来了  但是没有灵魂
You come back -- I'm sorry -- with no soul,
像打了鸡血的美国精神病人
like some peppy "American Psycho,"
直到圣人迪恩买了点神奇的"忘情水"
till saint Dean glues you back together again
把你又拼凑在一起
by buying you some magic amnesia?
你是真实的
You're real.
我也是真实的
I'm very real.
其他所有一切都只是"布景"
Everything between is what we call "Set dressing."
-不  -你还在我的牢笼中
- No. - You're still in my cell.
伙计  我们就住上下铺
You're my bunkmate, buddy.
你就是我的小婊子  彻头彻尾的小婊子
You're my little bitch, in every sense of the term.
萨姆
Sam.
-萨姆  -萨姆
- Sam! - Sam!
能听到我说话吗
You hearin' me?
看着我
Look at me. Hey!
我们要了结此事
All right, we got to button this up.
快点  我们离开这里
Come on. Let's get out of here.
快点
Come on.
(请保护你的饮用水)
(为三郡区域供水)
(市水厂)
见鬼
Aw, hell.
(公共水源)
[邪恶力量 第7季第2集]
该死的
Damn it.
谁说不是呢
You said it.
那些  不管是什么东西
Those... whatever-you-call-'ems...
利维坦
Leviathan.
没错
Right.
如果他们进入了水管
If they're in the pipes,
就像上了高速  四通八达
they got themselves a highway to anywhere.
算你们狠
Awesome.
好了
Okay.
那么  他走了
So, he's gone.
没错
Yup.
安息了
Rest in peace...
希望如此吧
if that's in the cards.
你个傻逼
Dumb son of a bitch.
他还跟我们做朋友呢
Well, he was friends with us, wasn't he?
还有比这更傻逼的事吗
Can't get much dumber than that.
走吧
Come on.
那些东西很快就会出来透气的
Those things will be coming up for air soon.
(市保护区  不得入内)
(洗车  支持斯托克维尔球队)
嘿  帅哥  醒醒
Hey. Wake up, sunshine.
快点起床 伙计
Up and at 'em, atom man.
小萨姆
Sammy.
-小萨姆  -小萨姆
- Sammy. - Sammy.
你已经睡了十二小时了  我觉得你休息够了
That's 12 hours straight. I'm calling that rested.
给你  补充水分
Here. Hydrate.
还有  食用蛋白质
And, uh, protein-ate.
在床上吃早餐
Breakfast in bed.
别太习惯了  给我看看你手
Don't get used to it. Let me see that hand.
哇哦  他要握你那小湿手了
Aw, he wants to hold your widdle hand.
真是太贴心了
How sweet.
你不会有事的
Yeah, you'll live.
好了  放松
All right, take it easy.
他们要渗透式入侵  有什么线索吗
So, ooze invasion -- any leads?
我让我所有的眼线盯着
I got all my feelers out.
无论他们想干嘛
Whatever they're up to,
绝不会象摩斯拉那样大摇大摆地走上大街的
it ain't -- it ain't about going Mothra down main street.
迟早会现身的
They'll turn up.
他们貌似十分渴望大展拳脚  不是吗
They seemed pretty eager to stretch their legs, you know?
是啊  现在说说我们另一个大问题
Yeah, well, now onto our other big problem.
你怎么样  别用"不错"来忽悠哥
How are you doing? And do not say "Okay."
不怎么好
I'm not okay.
你说呢
You think?
别那么凶  放松
Go a little easy.
鲍比  这事儿能松地了吗
There's nothing easy about it, bobby, okay?
我们装得像他能控制得了
We acted like he had everything under control.
我知道
I get it.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
听着  我也不想崩溃的
Look, I-I didn't exactly want to crack up, you know?
那究竟是怎么回事
What the hell happened back there?
已经不只是回忆的闪现
Well, it's not just flashbacks anymore.
那还有什么
Well, then what?
更像是
It's more like...
从裂缝里看到了一些东西
I'm seeing through the cracks.
什么意思
What does that mean?
就是说  我现在已经难辨真假了
It means I'm having a difficult time figuring out what's real.
幻觉吗
Hallucinations?
一开始是这样
For starters.
如果你开始出现幻觉了
Well, for starters, if you're trippin' hell's bells,
为什么要隐瞒呢
why would you hide that?
我并不是隐瞒  迪恩
I wasn't hiding it, Dean.
我  我只是不想说罢了
I-I was just not talking about it.
你们俩手头上的麻烦好像够多的了
I mean, it seemed like you two had enough going on as it was.
我  我只是想自己想办法控制住
Look, I-I just figured try to hold on to the safety bar
撑下来算了
and ride it out, you know?
我
I...
但幻觉却越来越具体真实了
But it's getting more specific.
具体都有些啥
As in, specifically what?
我勒个去  萨姆
What the hell, Sam?
我说过
I told you.
不  说真的
No, I mean, seriously,
这还有什么可说的
how do you -- how do you argue with that?
我知道  确实有点严重
I know. I-it's a problem.
等一下  我知道了
Well, wait. I got it.
那个魔头能在牢笼里海扁你
Why would the devil holodeck you a whole new life
干嘛还要放你出来过新生活呢
when he could just kick your ass all over the cage?
因为  用他的话说
'Cause, as he puts it...
你不能折磨一个
you can't torture someone
已经一无所有  没什么好失去的人
who has nothing left for you to take away.
说得太好了  萨姆
Very good, Sam.
好吧  懂
Okay, fine.
但如果这是幻觉
But this Malibu dream Mansion
是他为了让你有所失而制造的
that he -- he -- he makes for you to take away
就造了这么个后天启时代乱世吗
is this post-apocalyptic mess?
萨姆告诉他  必须得混乱
It had to be a mess, Sam,
否则你会怀疑这不是你的人生的
Or you wouldn't believe it was your life.
等一下  你不会现在也能看到他吧
Wait, are you seeing him right now?
你知道他不是真实存在的吧
You know that he's not real, right?
他也这么说你们的
He says the same thing about you.
我还是回去做事好了
I'm going back to work.
科学家们还无法解释这种现象
Scientists have no explanation
只能将其描述为一次"意外的月食"
for what astronomers can only describe as a "Surprise eclipse."
您很饥饿吧
We know you're hungry!
干吗不来比格森自制馅饼吧来饱餐一顿呢
Why not indulge yourself at Biggerson's homemade pie bar?
是卖馅饼的沙拉吧
It's like a salad bar but with pie!
《性感医生》下集预告
Next week on "Dr. Sexy, MD".
切耶尼·梅格诺普里斯医生震撼回归
Dr. Cheyenne Meganopolis makes a shocking return...
抱歉  医生
I'm sorry, Doctor.
我忘了作为主治外科医生就意味着
I forgot being head surgeon means
你可以肆无忌惮地对任何人开膛破肚
that you cut into whatever body you want
随意切取你中意的器官
and take out whatever organ pleases you
却不需要履行任何手续
without any paperwork whatsoever!
医生  你的健忘真让我遗憾
Well, Doctor, I'm sorry you're so forgetful.
(三城区治安官系统)
好了  至少他没蜷缩到水池底下
Well, at least he's not curled up under the sink.
是没有  他就安安静静地坐那儿
Yeah, no, he's just sitting there silently,
练习装弹
field-stripping his weapon.
你要干嘛
What are you doing?
把他的GPS打开  免得他又消失不见了
Turning on his GPS 'case he decides to fly the cuckoo's nest.
那你呢
And you?
你怎么样了
How are you doing?
说真的  鲍比
Seriously, Bobby.
他又不是中了巫术
It ain't like he's hexed, you know?
如果这是治不好的疯病呢
I mean, what if this is the kind of crazy you can't fix?
是啊  我...我也很担心
Yeah. I'm -- I'm worried, too.
但...就当哄哄我
But...humor me for a second.
你怎么样
How are you?
现在还顾得上我啊
Who cares?
你不觉得我们现在手头的事够多的了吗
Don't you think our mailbox is a little full right now?
-我没事  -好的
- I'm fine. - Right.
几个小时前
And weren't you pissed at him
他还没疯掉  也这么说的时候
when he said the same thing just a couple hours before
你不也生他的气吗
spilling his marbles all over the floor?
是的
Yeah, well...
我不是萨姆  好吧
I'm not Sam, okay?
我头脑清醒的很
I keep my marbles in a lead friggin' box.
我真的没事
I'm fine, really.
当然没事了
'Course, yeah.
你刚刚失去了一个最好的朋友
Just lost one of the best friends you ever had.
你弟弟现在一团糟
Your brother's in the bell jar.
炼狱中最邪恶的家伙在下水管道里乱窜
And purgatory's most wanted are surfin' the sewer lines,
但  对  对  我明白
but yeah, yeah, I get it. Right.
你...你没事
You're -- you're fine.
好的
Good.
当然了  如果你什么时候
'Course...if at any time
你决定承认那都是屁话
you want to decide that's utter horse crap,
像以前一样  我会一直...
well, I'll be where I always am --
在这陪你的
right here.
你是想跟我做双人瑜伽
What, you want to do couples' yoga
还是想去收拾那些坏家伙
or you want to get back to hunting the big bads?
闭嘴
Shut up.
你这白痴
Idiot.
是吗  去你的吧  曼宁
Yeah? Up yours, Manning.
我还是比你快0.06秒
I still got 0.06 on your time.
嘿  你们去哪了
Hey! Where were you guys?
我想我们回来得早了点
I guess we got here early.
听见浴室有奇怪的声音
Heard something weird coming from the showers.
你要干什么啊  威廉姆斯
Hey, what are you doing, Williams?
你这样会惹麻烦的
You're gonna get in trouble.
没错  斯考特  有可能啊
Yes, Scott. I probably am.
我想威廉姆斯是想说  斯考特
I think what Williams is trying to say, Scott,
我们饿疯了  才不管这些
is that we're too hungry to care.
(苏福尔斯综合医院)
朝急诊室的护士大喊
Crying to the E.R. nurse,
"天啊  饶了我吧"
screaming, "Mother mary, mercy!"
他们切开她的后背时
And when they opened her back up,
有三块海绵和一套夹具
three sponges and a set of clamps,
缝在她身体里  活像个皮纳塔(一种装着糖果的装饰品)
sewn up inside like she was a living pinata!
你可不能信任这些人
You can't trust these people.
下午好  女士们
Afternoon, ladies.
你好啊  医生
Oh, hello, doctor.
你好  盖恩斯医生
Hi, Dr. Gaines.
米尔斯小姐  你今天表现很好
So, Ms. Mills, you did excellent today.
就像我们说的  是一次标准的阑尾切除术
Just as we discussed, it was a textbook appendectomy.
那不错
That's good.
但你刚经历了一系列的大手术
But you have been through a serious surgical procedure.
我知道你很坚强
Now, I know you're tough...
但我希望你今晚别太勉强
...but I want you to take it easy tonight.
-没问题  医生  -好消息是
- Works for me, Doc. - The good news --
我给你开了些很好玩的止痛药
I put you down for some pretty fun painkillers.
我会先来看你的
I'll check in on you first thing.
你马上就能回家了
You'll be home in no time.
他很有风度  是吧
Charming, isn't he? Hmm.
你知不知道有研究表明
Did you know a study showed
四分之三的医生考试做过弊
3/4 of doctors cheat on their exams?
他可能都分不清你的阑尾和阴道
He might not know your appendix from your vagina.
嘿  小伙子  动作快点
Hey, there, Gunga Din. Buck up.
看起来我们有些坏消息了
So, it looks like we got some bad news for a change.
堪萨斯州北部  斯托克维尔
Stockville, North Kansas,
一所高中的游泳队大部分成员
most of a high-school swim team
在更衣室里被撕碎
got mangled to death in their locker room.
警察的说法含混其词
Cop-talk on the wire's kind of garbled,
说像是动物袭击
sayin' it looks like some kind of wild-animal attack.
他们说攻击他们的动物
They're saying that whatever attacked them
有橄榄球中后卫那么壮
was about the size of a linebacker.
这是条线索  迪恩
It's a lead, Dean.
好吧  但如果你想参加这次捕猎
All right, but if you think you're going out on a hunt...
不  我知道的  我不去  但你得去
No, I know. I'm not, but you are.
听着  鲍比是信息中转站
Look, Bobby's running the hub.
我现在分不清现实和幻觉
I'm 5150'd,
就只剩你去把这事搞明白了
which leaves you to follow this thing up.
萨姆  你现在处于精神崩溃状态
Sam, you're in the middle of a psychotic break.
几个小时车程就到了  迪恩
It's a couple hours' drive, Dean,
而且可能是那利维坦怪物
and it could be a Leviathan thing.
不行  你以为我会把你一人留在这吗
No, if you think I'm leaving you here alone...
那我呢  你当我不存在吗
Hey, what am I, chopped brains on toast?
我看着这孩子  你去吧
I can eyeball the kid. Go.
把你的心思放到有用的活上
Work off some of these nerves on something useful.
行
Fine.
你这躯壳可真瘦小
You got yourself an awfully small body.
既瘦小
Too small.
又无知
She didn't know anything.
连柜台都够不着
Can't even see over the counter.
瞧我这副...
Well, this one...
埃德加
"Edgar"
埃德加是爆破小组的员工
Edgar worked on something called a demolitions crew.
看到东西被炸飞  他显然有种满足感
Watching things blow up is apparently very satisfying.
"安妮"知道婴儿从何而来
"Annie" knew where babies come from.
要我说  这很恶心
Disgusting, by the way.
我很饿
I'm hungry.
我们都饿
We all are.
对了  说起这个...
Yes, about that...
对不起
I'm sorry!
Sorry?
他们活吞了游泳队
They ate the swim team.
如我所言  饥饿难耐
Like I said -- hungry.
这不是借口
That's no excuse.
那你要我怎么做
Well, what do you want me to do?
让他们老实点  我不管你用什么手段
Get them in line. I don't care how.
天呐  都上新闻头条了
For god's sake, it made the papers.
听着  老大  其实...
Look, the boss, honestly --
他只想知道这事处理好了
he just wants to hear it's taken care of.
那就赶紧把事办好
So take care of it quickly.
我不喜欢向他汇报坏消息
I don't like bringing him bad news.
听明白了吗
Are we clear?
事实上  我有个主意
Actually, I have an idea.
需要你帮忙
I could use your help.
小姑娘  有什么需要帮忙的吗
Little girl, can I help you?
你是性感医生吗
Are you a Dr. Sexy?
我是外科医生
Uh...I'm a surgeon.
你爸爸妈妈在哪呢
Where are your parents?
这是真的吗
Is it true?
外科医生可以肆无忌惮地对任何人开膛破肚
Surgeons can just cut into whatever body they want?
什么
What?
随意切取他们中意的器官
And remove whichever organs they please?
你究竟是从哪听来的
Where in the world did you hear --
我长大后要当一名外科医生
I want to be a surgeon when I grow up.
放开我
Let me go!
而且我现在就要长大
And I want to grow up now!
你好  我是伊恩·安德森特工
Hi. Special Agent Anderson, Ian.
让他进来吧
Yeah, okay.
我们驻点的警员出去买面包圈了
Our point cop's out on the doughnut.
我是法医  可以带你看下现场
Forensics. I can show you the layout.
请小心行走
And step lightly.
那边有一大堆限制级的恶心东西
We got a whole bunch of NC-17 shizznickle right over there.
好吧
Right.
该死
Damn it.
别出声  深呼吸
Shh! Just breathe deeply.
可我的手术定在明天
But my surgery isn't till tomorrow.
我是性感医生
I'm Dr. Sexy!
你的手术我说了算
Your surgery is when I say it is.
太不奇怪了
Not weird at all.
说
Yeah.
可以确定是那帮恶心的家伙干的
Well, we are positive for ick.
和小卡身上流出来的玩意儿一样
Same kind of stuff that came out of Cass.
而且游泳队有两个小孩依然下落不明
And, uh, two of the swim kids are missing.
他们偷了家里的一辆车
They stole one of their parents' cars.
我真的觉得威廉王子找对了姑娘
You know, I really think Prince William has found the right girl.
你说呢
What do you think?
你觉得这些
So, you think these, um,
利维坦也像夏娃一样
Leviathan things just jump into people,
会附身于人类
like Eve did?
我不知道  这说得通啊  不是吗
I don't know. It makes sense, right?
不管怎样  州警的监控录像
Anyway, uh, state troopers got surveillance cam
大概六小时前发现了那俩小孩
on the kids, about six hours old.
他们加油后朝达科他州边界的南部行驶
They're gassing up just south of the Dakota line,
我现在回你那儿
so I'm headed back your way.
我们再从鲍比家出发去追他们
We'll just track 'em from Bobby's.
好的  不错
Yeah. Sounds good.
你状态如何
How you doing?
还行
You know, uh, okay.
好的  坚持住  好吗
Okay. Well, hang in there, all right?
只是还行吗
Just okay?
哥们儿  我可是状态极佳
Man, I'm having a great day.
(病房停用待修)
米尔斯小姐  你下床做什么
Miss Mills, what are you doing out of bed?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
米尔斯小姐  你把我们吓了一大跳
Miss Mills, you gave us all a scare.
什么  不  我...
What? No, I...
你现在的病情
You can't be wandering
不可以那样四处走动
around the halls like that in your condition.
他把  他把
He took -- he took...
什么  谁
What? Who?
盖恩斯医生
Dr. Gaines?
米尔斯小姐  我们嘱咐过你别太勉强的
Miss Mills, we told you to take it easy, remember?
当然
Of course.
你那么四处走动是做什么呢
What in the world were you doing wandering the halls like that?
没事
Nothing.
缝合处有点儿痒
Um, my stitches were itching,
我只是想问问这是不是正常现象
and I just wanted to know if that was normal,
我肯定是昏倒了什么的
and I must have fainted or something.
我的伤口现在没事了
My stitches feel fine now.
米尔斯小姐你不能下床
Miss Mills, you can't get out of bed.
刚才那样的摔倒可能会撕裂缝合口呢
You could have ripped open your sutures with a fall like that.
可别让我再给你开刀
Don't make me go back in there.
好吗
Okay?
什么东西
What's that?
只是帮助你睡眠的药物
This is just something to help you sleep.
不  不用  我会睡得好的
No, that's okay. I'll sleep just fine.
这是医嘱
Doctor's orders.
我过会儿再来看你
I'll check on you later.
去死吧  魔鬼医生
You can kiss my ass, Dr. Monsterface.
天哪
Oh, god.
不  不
Oh, no, no.
如果这只是你可以任意掌控的梦境
Okay, if this is some dream and you got power over it,
为什么不结束它
why don't you just end it?
结束
End it?
你现在分不清孰真孰假
This -- you not knowing what's real,
神智一点点走向崩溃
the paint slowly peeling off your walls --
你想一想啊
Come on, man.
正是最有趣的时候  怎么可以结束
This is the sweet spot. Why would I end it?
地狱又没有线电视看
It's not like we got HBO in the pit.
只有你一个玩具
All I got is you,
看你在混乱中挣扎
floating over the coals
在绝望边缘寻找出路
with half a hope that you're gonna figure it all out.
只有一条出路  萨姆
There's only one way to figure it out, Sam.
完全由你掌控
It's up to you.
你再也无法承受的时候  就会结束
It ends when you can't take it anymore.
我想你擦枪或许就是做这个用处
I think maybe that's why we're cleaning our guns.
闭嘴
Shut up.
给我闭嘴
I said shut up!
萨姆
Hey, Sam.
你...
You, uh...
又有点小慌乱了吗
Havin' a little bag-lady moment, huh?
对不起
Sorry.
谢谢
Thanks.
知道吗  我经历过
You know, after...
这么多事情
everything...
这么多年  什么艰难险阻都见过了
all these years, all that we've been through...
你之前战胜过他  孩子
You beat the devil before, kid.
这次不一样了
It's kind of different.
没什么不同
Not really.
这次你同样会有办法的
You'll get a handle on this, too.
你会的
You will.
你已经不在地狱里了
You're not in hell anymore.
你在这里  和我们一起
You're here, with us.
你听明白了吗  萨姆
You hear me, Sam?
我知道了  鲍比
Yeah, I hear you, Bobby.
是找我的
Oh. That's my local.
你好
Hello?
鲍比·辛格吗
Bobby Singer?
我的医生是个怪物
My surgeon is a monster.
怎么回事
Come again?
他带走了我的话痨室友
He took my windbag roomie,
吃了她的肝脏
and he ate her liver.
他根本就不是医生
Except he wasn't -- he wasn't a surgeon.
他...
He...
听我说  他的脸...
Listen! His face was...
他的嘴是个可怕的...
His mouth was this horrible th--
-你是谁  -乔迪
- Who is this? - It's jody.
乔迪·米尔斯
Jody Mills.
乔迪
Jody?
米尔斯警长
Sheriff Mills.
知道了
Gotcha.
我现在没法叫支援
I can't exactly call a deputy here.
别装了  我们一起杀过僵尸
Come on, you and I killed zombies that one time.
我知道你能处理这档子事
I know you handle this kind of thing.
求你在他把我吃掉之前赶到
Please get your ass here to Sioux Falls general
苏福尔斯综合医院  辛格
before he eats me, Singer.
如果米尔斯警长不是做恶梦梦见
Well, either sheriff Mills is having
奥巴马医改方案成真
an Obamacare-insured opium dream
就是苏福尔斯综合医院出了食人案了
or something's eating folks down at sioux falls general hospital.
我不想伤你自尊...
Look, I don't want to bruise your ego or anything...
不不  没事
No, no, no. It's -- it's okay.
去吧  我来负责接电话
Go, go, go. I-I'll watch the phones.
那现在
So...
只剩下我们俩了
just you and me, huh?
(苏福尔斯综合医院)
你们俩怎么了
What happened to you two?
我打的
I did.
盖恩斯医生在哪里
Where is Dr. Gaines?
看病要走程序  懂吗
Oh, no, that's not how it works, okay?
如果你们想找医师看病
If you require a physician's attention,
先把这两份表填了
you're gonna have to fill out these forms.
交给我吧  护士
I can take over from here, nurse.
这两位
These...
小伙子需要马上接受治疗
youths obviously require immediate care.
这就是人类修复自己身体的地方
This is where they bring their bodies to be fixed.
他们认为这儿很安全
They consider it a safe place.
事实上  这里经常有人丧命
But the truth is, often they actually die here instead.
而且没人会起疑心  没开玩笑
And they never question it. I'm not kidding.
我们偷偷的进食  没人会知道
We can feed discreetly. No one will know.
只要我们在适当位置安插好人手
A few of us in the right positions,
每天都将是饕餮盛宴
and we could feast every single day.
我想就从护士长和人事科长开始
I'm thinking head nurse and the staff administrator for a start.
你确实有一手
I have to hand it to you --
这正是老大要的
It's exactly what the boss asked for.
-我的发散思维  -不错
- Out-of-the-box thinking. - Yes.
不用再当游泳队员了  孩儿们
You're off the swim team, boys.
是时候弃文从医了
Time to pursue a career in medicine.
先这样  跟我汇报
All right. Check in.
你不留下来吗
You won't stay?
我非常乐意为你抓个麻醉医师来
I would love to grab us a good anesthesiologist.
他还有另外的事情要我去做
He asked me to check into some other business in the area.
更何况  你做的很不错
Anyway, seems you've got things well in hand.
为什么他们不叫呢
Why can't they scream?
我事先切断了他们的声带
Oh, I severed their vocal cords, of course.
这可是个精细的活儿  多亏我技术好
It's a delicate procedure but very doable.
迪恩
Dean.
真贴心
Good thinking.
我刚刚
So, I, uh...
我跟踪了那些游泳队员  利维...什么的
I followed those swim-kid Levia...Whatever.
-到哪儿  -这里
- To where? - Here.
他们回城了
Well, back to town.
总之不是好事
And that ain't the good news.
什么
What?
我觉得他们可不止两个人
It ain't just two of them, I don't think.
你给鲍比打过电话了吗
Did you call Bobby?
打了  他有事在忙  我得行动了
Yeah, he's working his own case, I got to move,
我需要支援  也就是你了
and I need backup, and that means you.
等等  你确定要用我
Wait. You -- you sure about that?
我知道  你脑抽着呢
I know. You're bonkers.
不过还好  我只要你开着车别熄火
But, luckily, I just need you to keep the engine running
在后门等我
and wait by the back door.
只要你
Just don't, uh...
别让你家撒旦乱改我设的车台就好
don't let satan change my presets.
走吧
Let's go.
(西北入口)
她叫哈克特夫人  她再也没能回来
Her name is Mrs. Hackett. She never came back.
交给我吧
I'll check it out.
你先回去好好休息  我回头去看你
Now, you get some rest. I'll come by later.
鲍比·辛格  我的英雄
Bobby Singer, my hero.
你这是打了麻药昏了头
That's the roofies talking.
(停尸间)
足部手术
Foot surgery, huh?
今早死亡
Died this morning.
已解剖了  搞什么鬼
Already autopsied? What the hell?
你还好吧  萨姆  我指脑子
How you doing, Sam? In the head region?
魔鬼还在骚扰你吗
Devil still riding shotgun?
现在没  可是经常有
Not right now, but...Yeah.
或许我们该带你去看看  那什么
Maybe we ought to get you, I don't know, some --
干什么  找白衣天使吗
Some what? Some "Professional help"?
他们能怎样  迪恩
What are they gonna do, Dean?
只会给我塞一把药
Just stuff me full of pills.
我们得另想办法
We'll figure out some other option.
好吧
Okay. Yeah.
可你还有什么办法呢
But what are your other options?
记得马丁发疯的时候
You remember when Martin took his nosedive
举枪对着空气乱打吧
and started shooting at nothing?
没过多久就把自己折腾死了
I mean, his sweater unraveled fast.
-我不是马丁  -没错  可是你也疯了
- I'm not Martin. - No, but you are crazy.
不会就那么好起来  你很清楚  对不对
And that don't wash off. You get that, right?
你永远不可能好起来的  萨姆
You are never gonna be okay, Sam.
萨姆
Sam!
小萨姆
Sammy?
萨姆
Sam?!
糟了
Oh, crap.
见鬼  他们有五个
Oh, damn it. There's five of 'em.
来吧  我们走
All right. Come on.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
是的  听好了  当我们进去后
Yeah, and listen, when we get in there,
你可得振作点
You got to keep it together.
我  我会的
Yeah, yeah. I-I will.
如果你能看到路西法
'cause if you're seeing Lucifer,
你就有可能看到各种乱七八糟的东西
then you could be seeing all kinds of crap, okay?
你想都想不到
You just don't know.
这不是帮倒忙吗
How is this helping?
我是说  萨姆  你已经失控了
I'm just saying, Sam, you're out of control.
我在尽我所能处理这事了
I'm dealing with it the best I can.
处理吗
Dealing?
抱歉  那实在太搞笑了
I'm sorry. That's just funny.
你要怎么处理
I mean, how can you deal?
你觉得这是栋办公楼  对吧
You think this is an office building, right?
不好意思  你错了
Sorry. Wrong.
我们这是在哪里
Where the hell are we?
你认为我是迪恩
Oh, you think I'm Dean.
对了
Right.
你这个可怜又无知的狗崽子
You poor clueless son of a bitch.
离我远点
Stay the hell away from me.
你的世界由我主宰  明白了吗
Your world is whatever I want it to be, understand?
离我远一点
Just leave me alone!
看来你已经开始懂了
Now we're getting there.
匹诺曹看到牵着他的绳子了
Pinocchio's seeing his strings.
闭嘴
Shut up.
高潮部分来了
It's the big crescendo.
我说了闭嘴
I said shut up!
想把枪指着你能杀得了的人吗
Want to point that gun at someone useful?
试试你自己的脸
Try your face.
你想知道真相吗
You want to know the truth?
你想直接看到这事的结局吗
You want to skip to the last page of the book?
你知道该把枪瞄准哪里  牛仔
You know where to aim, cowboy.
这里就像个恶心的打包袋
It's like a friggin' doggy bag in here.
有什么需要帮忙的吗
Can I help you?
你还不如帮帮这家医院
You can maybe still help this hospital.
这份马马虎虎的文件是谁写的
Who's responsible for this sloppy bit of documentation?
我认识你
I know you.
不  你认错人了
No, you got the wrong guy.
鲍比
Bobby...
辛格  没错
Singer. Yes.
我们通过那个天使的双眼  看到你了
We saw you -- through the angel's eyes.
那你得试试失忆症了
Let's try for amnesia, then.
好极了
Fair enough.
情况不妙
Oh, this can't be good.
萨姆  萨姆
Sam? Sam!
看  又一个我
Oh, look. Another me.
萨姆  你在干什么
Sam, what are you doing?
迪恩  我以为我跟你在一起
I thought I was with you, Dean.
好吧
Okay.
我在这里
Well, here I am.
不  不  我  我不  我
No. No, I-I don't -- I...
我不能确定
I can't know that for sure.
你能懂我的意思吗
You understand me?
那我们就得一点点慢慢来了
Okay, then we're gonna have to start small.
我不记得我开车到这里来了
I don't remember driving here.
那是因为开车的是我
Well, that's because I drove.
你是这么认为的
You thought.
萨姆耳根子真软
Sam is very suggestible.
萨姆
Sam!
我们的谈话不需要开枪吧
This discussion does not require a weapons discharge!
看着我
Look at me.
别这样
Come on.
你不知道什么是真实的吗
You don't know what's real?
我去过地狱
Look, man, I've been to hell.
对于折磨我略知一二
Okay? I know a thing or two about torture --
足以知道地狱的感觉不同于
enough to know that it feels different
这个乱七八糟的东西带给你的痛苦
than the pain of this -- this regular stupid crappy this.
不  不  你怎么能确定
No. No, how can you know that for sure?
让我看看你的手
Let me see your hand.
不  不  不  那  那只受伤的手
No, no, no. The -- the gimp hand.
让我看看
Let me see it.
滚开  弗洛伦斯·南丁格尔(护士)
Smell you, Florence Nightingale.
这是真实的
This is real.
并非一年前  并非在地狱  而是现在
Not a year ago, not in hell -- now.
你受伤的时候我跟你在一起
I was with you when you cut it.
我给你缝的针
I sewed it up.
看
Look.
我们在疼痛方面做了许多改进
We've done a lot more with pain.
感觉是不同的  对吗
This is different -- right?
跟要把你逼疯的东西是不同的吧
Than the crap that's tearing at your walnut.
我也是不同的  对吗
I'm different. Right?!
好像是的
Yeah, I think so.
你确定吗  铺友
You sure about that, bunk buddy?
萨姆
Sam.
这招对我没用
Doesn't mean anything.
我是你的亲哥哥  不是吗
I am your flesh-and-blood brother, okay?
我是唯一一个可以
And I'm the only one who
名正言顺的立马揍你一顿的人
can legitimately kick your ass in real time.
你出来了
You got away.
我们把你弄出来了  小萨姆
We got you out, Sammy.
小萨姆
Sammy.
小萨姆  我是唯一一个
Sammy, I'm the only one who can --
相信我说的一切
Believe in that.
相信我  好吗
Believe me, okay?
你得相信我
You got to believe me.
你得把它当做第一准则并凡事以它为基础
You got to make it stone number one and build on it.
明白吗
You understand?
是的  是的  同意
Yeah. Yeah. Agree.
鲍比
Bobby. Hey.
警官是对的
Sheriff was right!
医院的事绝对是我们职权范围内的
The hospital thing's definitely our kind of thing.
我在太平间冲他们一个人开了"双筒炮"
I double-barreled one of them in the morgue.
用银子弹打他
Silver buck shot,
不管用
no effect.
只流出一些黑色的液体
Bled black ooze.
-利维坦在那吗  -我逃出来了
- Leviathan here? - I'm fallin' back.
我们在我家见面吧  我们重新部署
I'll meet you at the house. We can regroup.
鲍比见到了个活的
Bobby's got a live one.
好的  走吧
Okay, well, let's go.
等我们重新回到鲍比家
Look, when we get back to Bobby's...
没事了  迪恩  我很好
It's okay, Dean. I'm good.
没看见白兔
No white rabbits.
没有幻象
I'm not seeing anything.
那就好
Okay.
慢慢来
Baby steps.
不
Oh, no.
(禁止入内)
天啊
Oh, no.
看到他了吗
Any sign of him?
这地方被火烧了
That place was torched.
干这事的人目的明确
Somebody knew what they were doing.
你觉得鲍当时在家吗
You think Bobby was back there?
我不知道
I don't know.
鲍比
Bobby!
这是鲍比·辛格直通热线
This is Bobby Singer's direct hot line.
你不应该有这号码的
You should not have this number.
你不会在那个火坑里的
You cannot be in that crater back there.
我不能  如果你走了
I can't -- if you're gone,
我发誓会把我那心灵美丽的弟弟
I swear I am going to strap my "beautiful mind" brother
绑到车上的
into the car,
载着我们开车驶下码头
and I'm gonna drive us off the pier.
你问我过得怎么样
You asked me how I was doing?
一点也不好
Well, not good.
你说过你会陪着我
Now, you said you'd be here.
你在哪
Where are you?
鲍比
Bobby!
Bobby?
鲍比
Bobby!
温彻斯特
Winchester.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
看来  你们两兄弟有足够的能力
Apparently, you two are competent enough
能消灭我们
to warrant annihilating.
这可是恭维你呢
I'd take it as a compliment.
迪恩  快
Dean! Now!
萨姆
Sam.
小萨姆  醒醒啊
Sammy?! Hey, come on, now.
醒醒  我腿骨折了
Come on, I'm the one with the broken leg.
你得背我
You got to carry me!
萨姆
Sam?
别离开我  听见了吗
You stay with me, you hear?
男性 不到三十岁 颅脑损
Male, late 20s, head trauma.
颅内压有不断增加的迹象
Signs of increasing intracranial pressure.
也许我不是真实存在的
Hey, so maybe I'm not real.
人无完人
Nobody's perfect.
但我哪里也不去  萨姆
But I'm not going anywhere, Sam.
萨姆  小萨姆
Sam? Sammy!
他癫痫发作
Yeah, he's seizing.
给他注射十毫升镇定剂
Give him 10 of valium.
收到  我们刚开进苏福尔斯
Copy that. We're just pulling in to Sioux Falls.
苏福尔斯吗  苏福尔斯综合医院吗
Sioux Falls? Sioux Falls General?
不  不  不
No, no, no.
不  你得带我们去别的地方  任何地方
No, you got to take us somewhere else. Anywhere!
求你了
Please!
好的  伙计
Yeah, okay, buddy.